Guide to Carleen Hutchins papers M1734
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. General Files: Correspondence, Clippings, Photos, Papers, Notes
  - Gillen - Goren: Gillen and Co., 1971-71; Glassboro State College, 1977-79; Gleissner, Andreas, 1977-78; Glitte, R.; Goberman, Jean, 1974; Godal, Arne, 1958; Goddard Space Flight Center, 1980; Goldsmith, Kenneth, 1973; Goldberger, Mildred, 1968; Goldstein, Fred, 1985; Goldstein, Hans, 1967; Gomez, Oswald, 1953; Goren, Mayer B, 1964, 1958-1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Götz C. A. Jr. Musikinstrumente Export - Import., 1964 -2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Governor - Gretzem: Governor Wentworth Arts Council, 2005; Gillon, J. W. 1969; Graphic Impact, 1984; Grand, Louis L, 1963-92; Gretzem, Alfred, 1963-2005 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - The New Grove Dictionary of Music and Musicians I, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The New Grove Dictionary of Music and Musicians II, 1980-1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The New Grove Dictionary of Music and Musicians III, 1962-2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The New Grove Dictionary of Music and Musicians IV, 1997- 1998 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The New Grove Dictionary of Music and Musicians V, 1997- 1998 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Guggenheim Foundation, 1975-2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Guarneri - Guitars: Guarneri, 1967; Guild of American Luthier, 2005; Guitars and Makers, 1962-77, 1962-2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Guroff - Handbook: Guroff, Peter, 2004; Halbrook, Andronike, 1994; Hall, Harry H., 1933-37; Hall, Jody C.; Halstead Press, 1976; Hamilton College, 2004; Hammonasset Corp. Cases; Hammacher Schlemmer, 2001; Handbook of Acoustics, 1990-91, 1933-2004 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Hanson - Heifetz: Hanson, Constance C. 1982-87; Haran, Michael, 1976-78; Hardanger Fiddle, 1986-93; Harps, 1984; Harvard University, 1962-64; Harvard Press, 1959; Harvard Project Physics, 1964-67; Havas, Kató, 1971-74; Hearing, (The Sound Around Us), 1967; Heath, Oran, 1989-90; Heifetz, International Music Institute, 2003, 1959-2003 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Hendrian - Hercules: Hendrian, Barbara, 1958-98; Henley, Jean, 1985-87; Henson, Marjorie, 2000; Herlad News, 1968-74; Hercules Incorporated, 1967-74, 1958-2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Herschbach - Hobbie: Herschbach, Dudley, 1978-92; B. Hess lecture, 1994; Hewlett-Packard, 1979-83; Hibbert, I. V. 1973-76; Hill, Keith, 1984-85; Hobbie, Barbara, 1989-94, 1978-1994 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Hobbie - Hume: Hobbie, Barbara, 1989-94; Hoffman, Andrea, 1993; Hofstra University; Holder, Derwyn, 1992; Holmes, Protection. Co. 1983-85; Holvik, Martha, 1984; Hopkins, Debbie, 2003; Hopkins, Pandora, 1985; Howorth, Harmon, 1968-85; Huwyler, André, 2002; Hyde Manufacturing Co., 1957; Hume, Ben, 1997, 1957-2003 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Hunter - Ingard: Hunter College, 1980; Hurwitz, Robert, 1967-69; Indiana Botanic Gardens, 1976-79; Indiana University, 1968; Ingard, Uno, 1965, 1965-1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Iowa State University, 1967-1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Intercultural - Ithaca: Intercultural Association, 1974; Iselin, Nina, 1980-88; Israel, 1972; Italo-American String Instrument Co. Inc. 1980; Ithaca College, 1972-83, 1972-1988 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Itokawa - Johnson: Itokawa, Hideo, 1953; J. R. Music Supply Co., 1990; Jackson, Kevin, 1976-78; Jackson, Charles W. Mrs. (Dorothy), 1973; JASA 1983-93; Jeffrey, G., 1989-93; Jobelmann, India and Herman, 1967-96; Johnson, Dana, 1983-84, 1953-1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Jansson, E. V., 1970-1982 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, John Godshall I, 1984-1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, John Godshall II, 1992-2003 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, John Godshall III, 1992-2003 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, John Godshall IV, 1981-2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Jones - Kalamazoo: Jones, Wilfred, 1980-1981; Ju, David, 1994; Julliard School, 1998; Kalamazoo – Catgut Project, 1970-1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Kaplan - Kehoe: Kaplan, Daniel, 1986-1987; Karon, Jan, 1974-2001; Kasha, Michael, 1968-1970; Kay Elementrics Corp. 1977; Kehoe Specialty Distributors, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Keller – Kidd: Keller, Joseph B.; Kellert, Ellis, 1962-1964; Kelley, Dorothea, 1960-1963; Kelsey Nursery Services, 1959; Kennedy, Dave, 1971; Kershbergen, Johann, 1968-1974; Keuffel & Esser Co.; Kidd, Duncan, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Kienitz, Beate, 1983-1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Kim – Kirkorian: Kim, Young-Nam, 1982-1983; Kimura, Mari, 1989; Kirschner, Francis 1963-1992; Kitamura, Otoichi, 1984; Knowles Electronics, 1974-1975; Kobialca, Daniel, 1966-1984; Kohler, Jeanette, 1991; Korean Music, 1967; Kottick, Edward, 1983-1993; Koutzen, Nadia, 1987-1998; Krasner, Saul, 1983; Kraus, Serge, 1971; Kreider, Jack, 1982; Kirkorian, Paul, 1984-1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Krimmel - Larkin: Krimmel, Charles, 1987-1989; Kroyt, Boris (Budapest Quartet), 1959-1962; Krysa, Rachel, (Winnipesaukee Music Festival), 1997; Kupchynsky, Jerry, 1982; Kwoka, Chester S., 1966; Lahue, Michael, 1999; Laird, Paul, 1992; Lake Winnipesaukee Music Festival, 1996-1998; Lange, James N. 1963; Langman, Colin, 2000-2010; Larkin, Willard D. 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Lawergren, Bo T., 1971-1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Lawrence - Lenox: Lawrence, Anita, 1977; Lazaroff – Stockholm Museum, 1983-1990; Lazaroff, Semmy, 1975-1997; Leavitt, Virginia, 1969-1974; LeBlanc, Michael, 1974-1990; Lee, Robert K., 1992; Lehner, Eugene, 1959-1961; Lehigh University, 1974; Leibhardt, Edward, 1989-1999; Lenox Quartet (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Leszczynski - Library: Leszczynsk, David, 1996; Leuchter, Marvin, 1998-2001; Levine, Henry, 1958-1960; Libraries (general); Library of Congress, Harold Spiracke, 1958-1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Lidinsky – Lohmann: Lidinsky, William, 1984; Lincer, William; Lincoln, John, 1978; Lincoln Center, 1975; Lindevald, Ian M., 1988-1989; Lindkvist, Kent, 1980; Lindsay, David S. 1988-1996; Ling, Daniel, 1995-2001; Lingenfelter, Paul N., 1954; Link, John, 1998-2003; Lipson, Jerome J., 1959; Little, Dwight, 1973; Lloyds, Sue, 2003; Locker, Richard D., 1982-1993; Lockwood, W. R., 1968-1987; Loeb, James, 1966; Loesecke, Hildegarde, 1972; Loft, Abram, 1955; Lohmann, Theo, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Long - Lucchi: Long, Anton V., 1971-1992; Long, Hugh W., 1966; Lottermoser, W., 1968; Lougee, Arthur and Laura, 1963-1967; Lozon, Richard C., 1988; Lubman, David, 1983-1985; Lucchi, Giovanni, 1987-1994 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Lucent - Maluda: Lucent Technologies, 1997; Luening, Ethel C., 1975; Lupac, Emil; The Luthierie, 1982; Lyman, Melville H. 1961; Mac Donald Marquis George Foundation, Inc., 1971; Machine Design, 1982; MacCracken, Thomas, 1996; McCann, Steven, 1989; MacMillan Press Ltd. 1988; MacMillian Publishing Co., 1971-1983; Magashazi, John, 1986; Magram, Belle, 1975-1994; Maluda, John, 1981-1997 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Manhattan - Markert: Manhattan School of Music String Quartet, 1969; Manhattan Supply Co., 1977; Manley, S. W., 1989-1990; Mannina, Sergio, 1985-1991; Manzer, Linda, 1990-1994; Maple Leaf Music, Bruce Harvie, 1983; Marceau and Associates, 1998; Marck, Robert K. 1980-1981; Markert, John & Co., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Markevitch - Marshall: Markevitch, Dimitry, 1992-1999; Markot, Marina, 1977; Marlboro Music Festival, 1965-1968; Marshall, Joe F., 1952-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Marshall, Kenneth, 1983-1991 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Materials Research Society, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Materials - Mathews: Materials Research 1970; Mathews, William, 1994; Mathews, Violin Acoustics. Reviews, 1987-1990; Mathews, Max V.,1969-1986 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Matson – Maynard: Matson, Uno, 1976-1984; Matte, Gerard, 1975; Matsuda, Yoko, 1968-1997; Mattelson, Marvin, 1993; Maupertuis and Fletcher’s Translation; Mayer, Alfred M., 1874; Mayer, Fred, 1981-1983; Maynard, Chris, 1994; Maynard, Harry, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - McClure - McIntyre: McClure ,Lewis, 1967; McCracken, Charles, 1965; McCullough, John, 1968; McDougall, Marion, 1972-1976; McGill University, 1967-1968; McGilvray, Douglas and Elizabeth, 1970-1976; McGinnis & Marx, 1959; McGrath, Philip, 1986-1987; McIntyre, Michael, 1974-1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - McLennan, John E., 1980-2000 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - McLoughlin - Meisel: McLoughlin, Thomas, 1985-1986; McMillan, Gary, 1988-1989; Meadowbrook Inventions Inc., 1973-1983; Medwin, Herman, 1990-1998; Meier, W. M., 1973-1986; Meinel, Hermann, 1937-1940; C. Meisel, Inc., 1950 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Mellon - Mertens; Mellon Foundation, 1978; Melin, Virginia S.; Mell, Albert, 1986; Mellen, Robert, 1992; Mendelson, M. E., 1975-1977; Mendler, Rudolf, 1992-1993; Menzel, Richard, 1970-1995; Mertens, P. H., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan – Meyer: Metropolitan Music Co., 1954-1982; Meyer, H. J. G., 1987-1998; Meyer, Jürgen, 1975-1995 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Meyer - Miles: Meyer, Robert, 1980-1999; Metzner, James; Michelman, Joseph, 1948-1970; Michigan State University, 1969; Middletown Township Public Schools, 1973; Miles, John E., 1994-1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Mills - Missouri: Mills, Noel, 2002; Miller, Alan, 1992; Miller, Dayton C., 1967; Miller, Elizabeth, 1972-1973; Miller, Harry, 1975-1989; Miller, Kay (Minnesota Star Tribune), 1998; Miller, Joan E., 1985-2004; Miller, Theodore, 1991; Minafra, Mario, 1967-1980; Millman, Arthur, 1968-1971; Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Co., 1967; Minter, Jerry, 1975-1989; Mississippi State University (Dr. Terrance C. Conners), 1994; Mississippi University, 1975; Missouri Valley College (Endowment Fund), 1976-1984 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Missouri – Moenning: Missouri Valley College, 1973-1980; Mitra, Arun K., 1986-1994; Modern Maturity, 1988; Modern Music, 1971-1974; Moenning William & Son, 1967-1984 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Mogill - Monosoff: Mogill, Leonard, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1960-1961; Mohawk, 1990-1991; Moiré Patterns, 1970; Molenaar, Piet, 1977; Möller, Max, 1971; Molnar, Ronald, 1980-1993; Monadnock Music, 1972; Monosoff, Sonya, 1963-1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Montclair: Montclair Adult School, lecture and misc., 1968-1996; Montclair Business Service, 1960-1962; Montclair Chamber Music Society, 1976-1981; Montclair Chamber of Commerce, 1982-1997; Montclair College Women’s Club, 1969; Montclair Library, 1968-1996; Montclair Music Club, 1969-1978; Montclair Printing, 1953-1956 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Montclair - Montgomery: Montclair State University, 1964-1994; Montclair Women’s Club, 1970; Monteath, J. H. Co. 1961-1964; Montgomery, John, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Moore - Mowatt: Moore, Ward, 1982; Moral, Jesus Alonso, 1981-1996; Moran, William M., 1990; Moravec, Mary, 1987-1992; Moravia Foundation, 1971; Morris County Engineer’s Club, 1962; Morrow, Charlie, 1974; Morset, Lars Hernirk, 1998; Mortimer, Hervey, 1969-1980; Moscovitz, Shaler, 1974-1976; Mostovoy, Marc S., 1989; Mt. Holyoke College Archival Library, Elaine Trehub, 1992; Mountain Travel Gazette, 1974-1975; Mowatt, Don, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Müller, Helmut A., 1967-1994 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Multivox – Music: Multivox, Corporation of America, 1975; Munro, Edith, 1984-2004; Murray, Fancher M., 1994; Murdoch-Fairchild Miss Jacob, 1954-1961; Music Education National Conference, Article, 1973-1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Music Educators - Music Teachers: Music Educators Assn. of N. J., 1987; Music Library Association, 1974; Music Magazine, 1979; Music Perception, 1983-1999; Music Schools, 1975-1976; Music Teachers N. Y. State, 1963; Music Teachers National Association, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Musical - Mutch: Musical Acoustics, Reviews and Comments, 1976-1977; Musical Boxes; Musical Heritage Soc., 1982-1984; Musical Heritage Soc., CAS MHS Recording #4102, 1978-1995; Musical Instrument Societies, 1991; Musical Supply Company; Musicology, 1990; Mutch, William, 1976-1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Nagai, Yohei, 1971-1997; Nagy, Michael, 1988-1995 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Nakamura, Isao, 1978-1999 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Narada – National: Narada Publications, 1991; Naspo, Ronald, 1968-1986; National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, 1969; National Acoustics Laboratories, 1983; National Arboretum, 1979; National Bureau of Standards, 1966-1976; National Council Acoustical Consultants, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1969-1973; National Federation of Musical Clubs, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - National Foundation - Neuberger: National Foundation, 1960-1974; National Gallery, London, 1984; National Geographic Magazine, 1983-1984; National Music Council, 1981-1982; National Music Museum Newsletter, 2003; National Music Shop, 1954-1964; National Public Radio, 2005; National Research Council, 1984; Neuberger Museum, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Nevin - New Jersey Federation: Nevin, Ronald B., 1971-1972; New Timmerman, Ann, 1970-1992; New Brunswick Home News; New Hampshire University Summer School, 1999;; New Hampshire Audubon Soc., 1970; New Hampshire University of, 1996-2001; New Hampshire Profiles, 1964; New Jersey Chamber Music Soc., 1990; New Jersey Music Club, Belleville, 1962; New Jersey Federation of Music Clubs, 1973-1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - New Jersey State Council on the Arts, 1995-1999 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - New Jersey State Museum, 1970-1972; New Jersey Symphony, 1967-1994 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey Women - New York State: N. J. Women Project, 1986-1987; New School for Social Research, 1966; New Wilderness Foundation, 1976; New York Academy of Sciences, 1963-1983; New York State School of Music Assn., 1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - New York – Newark: New York Public Library, 1972-1975; New York University, 1960-1980; New York U. Physics Colloquium, 1978-1979; New York Viola Soc., 1993; New York Cello Soc.; New Zeland, 1980; Newark Boys Chorus School, 1973; Newark Museum, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Newfarmer - Noise: Newfarmer, Leo R., 1993-1997; Newman, Elaine, 1984-1992; Newport Research Corp., 1973; Newton’s Apple, 1984-1990; Nicole, Robert A., 1989; Nichols, Cecil E., 1977-1978; Nickell, Heny, 1977-1978; Nieder, Pat, 1992; Nigeria University, 1965; Nilsson Firma, 1971; Noel, Evan, 1992; Noise, 1986-1996 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - North Bennet – North Carolina: North Bennet St. School, 1988; North Bergen Pro Musicians; North Carolina Press, 1969-1973; North Carolina State University, 1975-1977; North Carolina University Chapel Hill, 1969-1983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - North Star - Northern Iowa: North Star Brand, 1969-1972; North Texas University, 1968-1971; Northeast Missouri State University, 1976; Northern Illinois University, 1975-1998; Northern Iowa University, Roger Hanson, 1984-1988 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Northern – Nuts: Northern Michigan University, 1966-1967; Northern Music Teachers Assoc., 1965; Northern Renaissance Instruments, Djilda Abbott, Ephraim Segerman, 1975-1991; Northwest Hardwood Specialty, 1963-1964; Norton, David, 1980; Norton, Joycelyn; Norway, 1974-1998; Nova, 1981-1984; Nussdorf, Steve, 1991-1993; Nuts-Kooks, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Oberlin – Ohio: Oberlin 1969-1996; Odoj, Hubert, 1988-1992; Ohio State University, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Oldham – Ortlieb: Oldham, Hugh W., 1976-1997; Olsen, Eric, 1976-1997; Oostens, Jean (Yolande), 1975-1977; Open University; Optical Society; Orduña Bustamente, Felipe, 1991; Oregon University, 1970; Organs, 1967; Oriental Instruments, 1965; Ormestao-Michaelsen, Hardinger Fiddle, 1980; Orsi, Giovanni, 1983; Ortlieb, Jean, 1974-1978 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Ortona - Ottawa: Ortona, Andrea, 1993-1998; Osborne, Harold, 1985-1986; Osborne, Sharon, 1977-1978; Ostergaard, Paul B., 1977-2004; Oteria, Frank, 2003; Ottawa, University, lecture, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Overlook - Oxford: Overlook Press, 1981; Ovington, Geoffrey, 1979-1993; Owen, Anthony J., 1976-1993; Owen, Chris Gordon, 1991-1992; Owen, Ieuan, 1977-1998; Owen, Larry, 1954-1978; Oxford University Press, 1976-1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Pacanovsky, Carl (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Pace, Antonio, 1973-2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Palmer, Merril, 1984-1997 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Palmgren - Pashler: Palmgren Steel Products, 1960; Pantheon Books, 1977-1979; Paradise, Paul, Paganiniana Publications, 1976Paris, 1971; Parisot, Aldo, 1973-1977; Park, Cynthia, 1981; Parsons, Donald F., 1988; Parsons, Priscilla, 1992; Partsch, Harry; Parzik-Tanasijevic, Lidija, 1985; Pasachoff, Jay M., 1987-1989; Pashler, P. E., 1964-1986 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Pasqualini – PCB: Pasqualini, Gioacchino, 1948; Passaic Valley High School, 1971; Patterson, Blake R., 1973; Patterson, K. B., 1969; Paul, David M.; Paulin, Jorge, 1997; PCB Piezotronics, Inc. 1969-1994 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Peabody – Peresson: Peabody, Baltimore, 1963-1984; Pei, Mario, 1968; Peidar Enterprises Co., 1981-1984; Pelzl, James C., 1978-1979; Pennsylvania State University, 1964-1973; Pennsylvania State University, Courtney B. Burroughs, 1996-1999; Pennsylvania String Teachers’ Assoc., 1967; Peresson, S. 1991 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Performing Groups (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Peri – Piano: Peri Press, 1986; Perrin, Robert, 1982-1998; Perry, David, 1991; Perry, Joan, 1983-1995; Peskin, Richard L., 1979; Peters, Jack, 1970-1975; Petersen, W. M., 1977-1980; Philadelphia Composers Forum, 1961-1967; Philadelphia Library, 1967; Philadelphia Orchestra, 1965; Phillips International, 1997; Philomusica N. Y. Chamber Ensemble, 1971; Physiology of Sound, Davis, Hallowell, 1961; Piano, F.L. Curzon, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Pirastro – Poland: Pirastro Strings; Pisani, R., 1974; Pisters, Alfons, 1980; Pitaro, Laurence, 1968-1969; Plain-Switzer, Karen, 1968-1994; Plainfield Symphony Society, 1959; Plastics for Violins; Poland, conferences, 1985-1996 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Pollard, Howard, 1980-2003 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Pollens – Primavera: Pollens, Stewart; Orille, Polly L., 1962-1971; Polysand Products, 1976; Pompidou, Georges, IRCAM, 1977-1980; Portnoi, Henry, 1968-1986; Poulos, James T., 1969-1975; Povolny, Jiri, 1990-1995; Powell, Wilson, 1969-1974; Praetorius, Michael; Previtera, Mario, 1969; Prier, Peter; Priesing, Dorothy, 1975-1997; Primavera, Adolph, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Princeton, Museum, 1965; Princeton Press, 1963-1965; Princeton University, office, 1979-1998 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Princeton – Professional: Princeton University, lecture, 1968; Princeton University, Ford Foundation, Scanion, 1974; Printers, 1989; Pro Musica Antiqua; Professional Audio Video Corp., 1981; Professional Music Teachers Guild, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Programs (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Proskauer - Publications: Proskauer, Richard, 1967; Proskouriakoff, Tania, 1971-1973; Pruyn, Peter, 1967-1968; Psychoacoustics; Publications (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Publishers I (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Publishers II (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Purdue – Quigley: Purdue University, 1984; Puterbaugh, W. H., 1967-1968; Pye, James, 1981-1983; Pyle, Robert W. Jr., 1984; Pyne, Joan, 1981-1982; Quartet Congress, 1989; Queen, Daniel, 1997; Quigley, Margery, 1959-1968 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Rabi - Railway: Rabi, Helen, 1959; Radcliffe Inst. for Independent Study, 1965-1966; RCA Laboratories Colloquium, 1979; Radio Corp. America, H. F. Olson, 1969; Radstake, Pim, 1997-2000; Rafferty, Michael P., 1983; Raila, Ronald, 1973; Railway Express (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Rakowski, Andrzej, 1973-1998 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Randerson, John T. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Ramakrishna – Reed: Ramakrishna, B.S., see Raman, 1997; Random House, 1971; Ratajak, William P.; 1972-1973; Ray, Carl, 1966-1974; Readers Digest, Canada, 1984; Recording Requests, 1968; Recording Violin, 1964; Reddy, K. C., 1981; Reed, Reba, 1962-1971 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Readers Digest, 1990-1998 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Rehearsal - Research: Rehearsal Club, 1970-1975; Reid, Joseph V., 1968; Reid, Warren, 1992-1993; Reinicke, Walter, 1973; Reller, Austin F., 1990-1995; Reprint Requests, 1962-1969; Research Papers (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Restivo – Reviews: Restivo, Shirley, 1976-1980; Retallack, Dorothy, 1970; Reuter, Fritz, 1984-1992; Reviews, Books, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Reynolds, Alfred G., 1967-1992 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Rhode – Rivinus: Rhode Island University, 1969-1977; Rhodes, Samuel, 1985; Ricci, George, 1991; Rice, Helen, 1980; Richardson, Dean, 200-2004; Richardson, Bernard E., 1993-1995; Rickard, James, 1990-1992; Ridgefield Conn. Library, 1982; Riggin, Cynthia, 1977; Riley, Maurice W., 1992; Rimski-Korsakov, A.V.; Risset, Jean C., 1993; Rivinus, David, 1974-1985 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Roberts – Rocaboy: Roberts, Gareth, 1989-1992; Roberts, Hank, 1992-1994; Robertson, Bruce M., 1973-1988; Robinson, Bernard, 1974; Robinson, James, 1972-1973; Rocaboy, Francoise, 1988-1997 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Roche - Rockefeller: Roche Research Soc., 1963-1964; Rochester Music Photo Copy Service Co., Inc., 1973; Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1982-1983; Rockefeller Foundation, 1965-1972; Rockefeller Foundation, Martha Baird, 1965-1979; Rockefeller University, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Rodgers – Rose: Rodgers, Oliver, 1990-1995; Rogers, Kenneth C., 1980; Roselli, Maureen, N.J. State Council of the Arts, 1997; Rose, John, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Rosevear, F.B., 1962-1999 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Ross- Royal: Ross, Arthur C., 1969-1975; Ross, Justin H., 1970-1992; Rossing, Thomas D., N. Illinois U., 1998-2002; Roth, David, 1978; Rothman, Tony, 1993-1994; Rotunda, Joseph, 1983-1991; Rowell, William, 1998; Royal Academy of Sciences (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Rubert – Russian: Rubert, M.P., 1972-1980; Rubin, Carol, 1982-1991; Rudie, Robert, Riverside School of Music, 1965-1978; Rudin, Joel, 1988; Ruff, Willie, bassist, 1969; Russell Sage College, 1986; Russian, 1973-1996 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Russo - Sacksteder: Russo, Barbara J., 1985; Rutgers University, Mechanical Engineering Colloquium, 1979; Rutgers University, 1962-1980; Ruthström, Olof J., 1979-1994; Sacksteder, Richard, 1977-1995 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Safety Lab (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Saint - Sapere: Saint Andrews Presbyterian College, 1980-1989; Saint Benedicts College, Atchinson Kansas, 1968; Saint Paul Machinery MFG Co., Salchow, William, Bowmaker, 1969; Sanders, F. A., 1950; Samo Šali, M. Sc., 1997; Samuelson, Werner, 1982; Sanford, Roy D., 1982-2002; Sandia National Laboratories, 1982-1984; Sangster, E. H., 1956-1964; Santa Fe Spruce Co., 1982; Sapere, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Sasselov – Scanlan: Sasselov, Dimitar D., 1992; Saunders, Silvia, 1962-1989; Sbernini, Luca, 1983-1993; Scandinavia, 1982; Scandinavian Violin Makers Assoc., 1969; Scanlan – Morse – Fortier, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Scarsdale - Schirmer: Scarsdale, 1969-1977; Scelba, Vincent A., Clifton, N. J., Schaffert, Arthur H., 1972; Schauffler, R. H., 1954; Schelleng, Charles, 1990; Schinke, Karl B., 1971-1994; Schirmer, G., 1957 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Schleske, Martin, 1991-1999 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Schmid - Schuch: Schmid, Charles, 1990; Schmidt, John P., 1982-1999; Schneider, John, 1980Scholastic Magazine, 1967-1968; Schoutens, Jacques E., 1986-1988; Schradieck, Alice, 1968; Schroeder, H. J., 1963; Schubach, Paul, 1975-1992; Schuch, Steve, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Schueman - Schumacher: Schueman, Dale, 1968; Schultz, Michael J., 1988-1991; Schultz, Theodore, 1987; Schumacher, Carolyn, 1977-1988 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Schumacher, Carolyn, 1977-1988 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Schumacher, Robert, 1972-1987 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Schumacher, Robert, 1988-1996 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Schuman - Scientific: Schuman, Daniel, 1961-1973; Schwartz, David, 1998-1999; Schwartz, Robert F., 1972-1989; Schwarz, Sanford, 1972; Science and Art, 1968; Science News, 1076-1994; Scientific American, Freeman, W.H. & Co., 1966-1984 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Scientific American, 1959-1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)